gumtree.in 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Your Local Classifieds

Gumtree.in has established its privacy policy to explain how your information within the purview of Gumtree.in is protected, collected and used. This policy may be updated by Gumtree.in. Gumtree.in will post notices of its policy changes on the Gumtree.in site at: <http://www.gumtree.in/privacy-policy-p26> You must review the policy on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes. 

**PRIVACY PROTECTION**

Gumtree.in does not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other similar sites. Gumtree.in recommends its customers to keep their password safe and do not remember it on public (shared) computers (Internet-cafe, college, library, family computer etc). Gumtree.in does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If Gumtree.in learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Gumtree.in will remove that posting. Gumtree.in, or persons who post on Gumtree.in, may provide links to third party websites, with different privacy policies. Gumtree.in is not responsible for, nor have any control over, those third party websites. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Gumtree.in collect traditional contact information such as your name, mailing and/or billing address, phone number and email address for few purposes: to send selfpublishing and confirmation emails, to authenticate user accounts, to provide subscription email services, to register for forums, to process any credit card charges, etc.

Your personal information may be collected by Gumtree.in if you provide it in the feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or other publishing areas of the website.

Should you expect your personal information to be private please do not post any personal information on Gumtree.in site. Standard web log entries for each page served, including visitor´s IP address, page URL, and timestamp are collected by Gumtree.in web logs in order to help diagnose problem with Gumtree.in servers, to administer Gumtree.in site, and to otherwise enhance visitor´s use of Gumtree.in sites and services. 

**COOKIES**

Gumtree.in.com set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as remembering your personal settings. The user may choose to disable, adjust enabled cookies or delete cookies by configuring the web browser. But it may result in the unavailability of some functions and features in this website. This website will not share any personal information with third parties. 

Advertisements appearing on this web site may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement.     
Third party plugins used for authentication and social media sharing may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the service.  
We use Google Analytics which collects visitor activity anonymously, to help us to know how vistors use our site. For Google Analytics privacy policy and to find out how to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

 **DATA STORAGE**

Gumtree.in stores in its database all user generated content (classified ads, forums, guestbook postings etc.) even after they are deleted, as well as can archive such data elsewhere. Gumtree.in indefinitely stores web logs and other records. Registered members can access and update personal account information through the account homepage. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Gumtree.in may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Gumtree.in may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-party; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Gumtree.in, its users or the general public. Gumtree.in complies with the provisions of C.R.S. § 6-1-716 pertinent to the breaches of security notifications effective September 1st, 2006. 

**GLOBAL USE**

By providing us with data and by visiting Gumtree.in you acknowledge and agree that due to the global use of Gumtree.in we may use the data collected in the course of your use of our site and/or services for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications to you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Data provided to Gumtree.in may be stored on servers throughout different jurisdictions. User agrees to consent to transfer of such data to different locations.
